Showdown Between Blue Cop and Wild Guardy!
Are you sure you're ready for this?
Just go ahead and shoot!
Woah!
Here comes the next one!
Wow!
Thank you, thank you.
Those are some skills.
Never missed a shot.
Truly a hunter in the wilds who never ever misses his mark!
Fleta Z, as of today, we're a team!
Once again, thank you for joining us!
Thank you for having me, Jun.
Huh?
What's that on Mega Trucker's head?
Aah!
I am terribly sorry about that.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
Crest?
Just as I thought. You're all here.
What brings you two here?
Hm. I see that one's been sealed.
I kept my promise!
Now it's your turn to do me a favor.
And what's that?
Tell me the deal with you and Wild Guardy! I want to know everything!
I would like to know as well.
Alright. Where should we begin?
How about when you used to be a Star Guardian on planet Machina?
Star Guardian?
What's that?
An elite force selected to guard Deus Machina, the mother computer of planet Machina.
Blue Cop was chosen among the best of the Metal Cardbots to become one.
I vowed to become a great Star Guardian just like Blue Cop.
However,
My dream was never fulfilled when planet Machina was destroyed.
I managed to escape, and was left to wander the vast universe.
After a long time drifting through space, Wild Guardy crashed down on Earth.
Crashed?
Did your escape pod malfunction?
We don't know.
He was in really bad shape when we found him.
Master! This looks bad...
Sebastian. Turn the car around. Let's take him back to the villa.
Uh- yes, Master!
Fortunately, the villa was equipped with everything we needed for repairs,
because my dad is the CEO of a car company, and my mom a doctor of robot engineering.
At first, we couldn't understand each other.
But even then, we shared a connection.
So this... is planet Earth?
Yes. It's where I was born and raised.
So, what's your name?
In your language, it's Wild Guardy.
I'm Crest.
Let's be friends.
So... That means Crest is like your savior, then?
Yes. He is also a very precious friend that I made on this planet.
A friend?
Then we saw on the news that mysterious robots have been showing up in Mowtown.
We knew right away.
That they had to be Metal Cardbots from planet Machina, just like Wild Guardy.
So, Crest... the reason you transferred here was...
To find out just who these robots were.
Although planet Machina is gone, I can still prove
that I can surpass even a Star Guardian if I can defeat Blue Cop!
I think you may have a mental illness.
You're pretty much stalking Blue bro here.
It might be better for you to spread your wings and be free.
You simpletons have no clue about the loneliness and woes
of someone with the dream of becoming the best!
What?!
I will rise above the Star Guardian and become king of the Metal Cardbots!
What is this guy even going on about?!
If that's what you want...
I will give you a chance.
What?!
Huh?
Yup! In return, you have to promise to join our team if you lose.
Sounds interesting.
Take them on, Wild Guardy.
What?!
Crest, not you too...
But... if you lose, you have to hand over the Metal Breath. Do you accept?
I accept!
No! You mustn't, Jun.
Are you afraid, Blue Cop?
No, it's not that-
You guys... you weren't thinking about having your duel in the middle of my car center, were you?!
I think we better find another location.
Actually... I think I know the perfect place. If you'd follow me, please.
Now!
Let us begin!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
What's this?
That's not Blue Cop!
I said we'll take you on!
But I never said it would be a one on one match!
If you want the Metal Breath, you'll have to get through all of us first!
What?!
Don't worry about it. I'm sure you can handle them all.
I'll finish them with one strike.
Alright then! Let's do this!
Yeah!
Mega Trucker, Mega Power Tackle!
No one can stop the unstoppable! Mega Trucker! Raah!
I don't even need to try. I can dodge you with my eyes closed.
Next!
Mega Trucker, come back!
That didn't even take ten seconds...
I can't believe it...
Phoenix Fire, you're up!
Ok!
Speed attack! Water Splash!
Water Splash!
Get back here!
Look out behind you!
Wild Slash!
Phoenix Fire, are you alright?
He's too strong...
Jun, you need to get serious!
I know.
Your turn, Mega Ambler!
Don't think that changing the players will change the outcome.
You should really learn some manners, kid.
Crest is right. Stop wasting my time.
Just show me what you've got.
What an attitude on this guy.
His nose is so high in the air!
Jun. We are ready whenever you are.
Alright! It's time for some rapid-strike attacks!
Mega Ambler, Forceps Crush!
Forceps Crush!
Shadow X, Spinning Cutter!
Spinning Cutter!
Haha! Better watch your head, buddy!
Dexter!
Spear Thrust!
Wild... Slash!
Jun! Send me out there!
No matter who you send out, the result will be the same!
Fleta Z, setup-
Hold on, Jun.
Blue Cop?
Send me out this time.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Don't worry, Blue Cop. I can finish him.
That's not the problem. Please. Let me, Fleta Z.
...I understand. Please go ahead.
At last you show up, Blue Cop.
I thought you'd be the finale, but I see you're ready to fight now.
When planet Machina was destroyed, I was alone too.
I spent ages wandering through space alone.
When I finally reached this planet, I found my kind again. And I cannot bring myself to hurt any of them.
What a pathetic excuse...
Just let me defeat you!
I have crawled back up from the brink of death!
Endlessly honing my skills to become stronger!
I am the one who is fit to be Star Guardian!
Haven't you figured it out yet?
What?
Blue Cop said that he doesn't want his friends to get hurt anymore!
When are you going to realize that includes you?!
Stop pretending to be so righteous!
This can't be... my sword!
Blue Cop!
Let's finish this, Jun!
Infinity...
Force...
Break!!
Wild Guardy!
Why...
...why can't I beat him...?
Does this mean I'm not cut out to be a Star Guardian?
That's not true, Wild Guardy.
I don't need your empty words...!
I mean it.
Deus Machina told me, right before planet Machina collapsed,
that I must use the Metal Breath, to find a friend.
A friend...?
Are you sure it's okay, Crest?
I made a promise.
Metal Cardbot, Change Up!
Wild Guardy, sealed!